{
    "Questions": [
        {
            "question": "For which operations will the SAP Gateway server compute and return a new ETag in a response header? There are 2 correct answers to this question",
            "options": [
                "Delete",
                "Put",
                "Post",
                "Get"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": [
                "Put",
                "Post"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What happens if you execute an app that contains the following bootstrap file? Please choose the correct answer.\n <script src=\"resources/sap-ui-core.js\" id=\"sap-ui-bootsrap\" data-sap-ui-libs=\"sap.m\" data-sap-ui-xx-bindingSyntax=\"complex\" data-sap-ui-resourceroots='{\"sales.reporting\":\"/\"}'></script>",
            "options": [
                "The bootstrap will load and the application will run successfully but without a theme",
                "The bootstrap will load and the customer-defined default theme will be used",
                "The bootstrap will NOT load and the application will produce an error message that the theme is missing",
                "The bootstrap will load and the SAP default theme will be used"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "The bootstrap will load and the application will run successfully but without a theme"
        },
        {
            "question": "For which operations will the SAP Gateway server compute and return a new ETag in a response header? There are 2 correct answers to this question",
            "options": [
                "Delete",
                "Put",
                "Post",
                "Get"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": [
                "Put",
                "Post"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What happens if you execute an app that contains the following bootstrap file? Please choose the correct answer. <script src=\"resources/sap-ui-core.js\" id=\"sap-ui-bootsrap\" data-sap-ui-libs=\"sap.m\" data-sap-ui-xx-bindingSyntax=\"complex\" data-sap-ui-resourceroots='{\"sales.reporting\":\"/\"}'></script>",
            "options": [
                "The bootstrap will load and the application will run successfully but without a theme",
                "The bootstrap will load and the customer-defined default theme will be used",
                "The bootstrap will NOT load and the application will produce an error message that the theme is missing",
                "The bootstrap will load and the SAP default theme will be used"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "The bootstrap will load and the application will run successfully but without a theme"
        },
        {
            "question": "For which operations will the SAP Gateway server compute and return a new ETag in a response header? There are 2 correct answers to this question",
            "options": [
                "Delete",
                "Put",
                "Post",
                "Get"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": [
                "Put",
                "Post"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What happens if you execute an app that contains the following bootstrap file? Please choose the correct answer. <script src=\"resources/sap-ui-core.js\" id=\"sap-ui-bootsrap\" data-sap-ui-libs=\"sap.m\" data-sap-ui-xx-bindingSyntax=\"complex\" data-sap-ui-resourceroots='{\"sales.reporting\":\"/\"}'></script>",
            "options": [
                "The bootstrap will load and the application will run successfully but without a theme",
                "The bootstrap will load and the customer-defined default theme will be used",
                "The bootstrap will NOT load and the application will produce an error message that the theme is missing",
                "The bootstrap will load and the SAP default theme will be used"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "The bootstrap will load and the application will run successfully but without a theme"
        },
        {
            "question": "For which operations will the SAP Gateway server compute and return a new ETag in a response header? There are 2 correct answers to this question",
            "options": [
                "Delete",
                "Put",
                "Post",
                "Get"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": [
                "Put",
                "Post"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What happens if you execute an app that contains the following bootstrap file? Please choose the correct answer. <script src=\"resources/sap-ui-core.js\" id=\"sap-ui-bootsrap\" data-sap-ui-libs=\"sap.m\" data-sap-ui-xx-bindingSyntax=\"complex\" data-sap-ui-resourceroots='{\"sales.reporting\":\"/\"}'></script>",
            "options": [
                "The bootstrap will load and the application will run successfully but without a theme",
                "The bootstrap will load and the customer-defined default theme will be used",
                "The bootstrap will NOT load and the application will produce an error message that the theme is missing",
                "The bootstrap will load and the SAP default theme will be used"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "The bootstrap will load and the application will run successfully but without a theme"
        },
        {
            "question": "For which operations will the SAP Gateway server compute and return a new ETag in a response header? There are 2 correct answers to this question",
            "options": [
                "Delete",
                "Put",
                "Post",
                "Get"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": [
                "Put",
                "Post"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What happens if you execute an app that contains the following bootstrap file? Please choose the correct answer. <script src=\"resources/sap-ui-core.js\" id=\"sap-ui-bootsrap\" data-sap-ui-libs=\"sap.m\" data-sap-ui-xx-bindingSyntax=\"complex\" data-sap-ui-resourceroots='{\"sales.reporting\":\"/\"}'></script>",
            "options": [
                "The bootstrap will load and the application will run successfully but without a theme",
                "The bootstrap will load and the customer-defined default theme will be used",
                "The bootstrap will NOT load and the application will produce an error message that the theme is missing",
                "The bootstrap will load and the SAP default theme will be used"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "The bootstrap will load and the application will run successfully but without a theme"
        },
        {
            "question": "For which operations will the SAP Gateway server compute and return a new ETag in a response header? There are 2 correct answers to this question",
            "options": [
                "Delete",
                "Put",
                "Post",
                "Get"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": [
                "Put",
                "Post"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What happens if you execute an app that contains the following bootstrap file? Please choose the correct answer. <script src=\"resources/sap-ui-core.js\" id=\"sap-ui-bootsrap\" data-sap-ui-libs=\"sap.m\" data-sap-ui-xx-bindingSyntax=\"complex\" data-sap-ui-resourceroots='{\"sales.reporting\":\"/\"}'></script>",
            "options": [
                "The bootstrap will load and the application will run successfully but without a theme",
                "The bootstrap will load and the customer-defined default theme will be used",
                "The bootstrap will NOT load and the application will produce an error message that the theme is missing",
                "The bootstrap will load and the SAP default theme will be used"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "The bootstrap will load and the application will run successfully but without a theme"
        }
    ]
}